We got that puppy shine in. Look at that blue. It came right back to life.
Yes, pretty much polished and protected. Buffed it out, made great.
And waxed it. Now the front protected.
At this completely UV protected and buffed out, we've got the toned cleaned,
waxed as well as all the metal.
Breath that blue right back out.
And we're able to polish the metal as well as protect the plastic.
And we got all of this looking fantastic.
Now we're able to even to polish and protect these.
We got the wheels looking shiny. Nice and cleaned up.
Nice and shiny. We are looking good.
I was able to put some UV protected on these handles as well.
We got the bumper buffed out as well.
And we got looking sharp. Real sharp. Real sharp.